Super bad. But in a good way.
Sinister Squad is a fantasy, action, horror film directed by Jeremy M. Inman.
When a supernatural cult threatens Earth, Alice must assemble a team of
fairy tale villains to face the literal forces of Death.
Rumpelstiltskin, played by Johnny Rey Diaz.
Alice, played by Christina Licciardi.
Goldilocks, played by Lindsay Sawyer.
Gelda, played by Talia A Davis.
Bluebeard, played by Trae Ireland.
Piper, played by Isaac Reyes.
Jai Stephen Courtney (; born 1985 or 1986) is an Australian actor.
Courtney started his career as a teenager with small roles in film and television, and
studied acting at the Western Australian Academy of Performing Arts.
After early supporting roles in Hollywood projects, he gained recognition for playing Dauntless leader Eric Coulter in The Divergent Series (2014–2015), Kyle Reese in
Terminator Genisys (2015), and supervillain Captain Boomerang in the DC Extended Universe films Suicide Squad (2016), and The Suicide Squad (2021).
He received praise for his performance as a corrupt debt collector and the
main antagonist in the independent film Buffaloed (2019).
Courtney's other notable credits include the Hollywood films I, Frankenstein (2014), Unbroken (2014), and The Exception (2016), the Australian films Felony (2014), The
Water Diviner (2014), Storm Boy (2019) and 100% Wolf (2020), and the television series Stateless (2020), The Terminal List (2022) and Kaleidoscope (2023).
He also portrayed the title character in the Melbourne Theatre Company's production of Macbeth
(2017), and hosted the Australian reality competition series The Summit (2023).
In 2025, he starred in the survival horror thriller  Dangerous Animals.
The tone is dark.